[
    {
      "questionNo": "Q1",
      "question": "Sam finds a book labelled 37. What number comes before 37?",
      "options": [
        "37",
        "38",
        "36",
        "39"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q2",
      "question": "Sam finds a book labelled 52. What number comes after 52?",
      "options": [
        "53",
        "52",
        "55",
        "54"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q3",
      "question": "Sam spots the book with number 100. What number comes before 100?",
      "options": [
        "97",
        "98",
        "100",
        "99"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q4",
      "question": "Thereâ€™s a book labelled 245. What number comes before 245?",
      "options": [
        "246",
        "244",
        "243",
        "250"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q5",
      "question": "A book with 387 needs to be shelved. What number comes after 387?",
      "options": [
        "386",
        "388",
        "389",
        "390"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q6",
      "question": "Sam has the book 120 but is missing the next one. What is the successor of 120?",
      "options": [
        "121",
        "119",
        "125",
        "115"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q7",
      "question": "Sam is arranging books near 300. What is the predecessor of 300?",
      "options": [
        "301",
        "298",
        "299",
        "305"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q8",
      "question": "The book labelled 512 is missing its successor. What is the successor of 512?",
      "options": [
        "511",
        "514",
        "510",
        "513"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q9",
      "question": "Sam places the book 909. What is the successor of 909?",
      "options": [
        "908",
        "911",
        "910",
        "905"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "questionNo": "Q10",
      "question": "Sam finds a book labelled 835. What is the predecessor of 835?",
      "options": [
        "833",
        "834",
        "836",
        "840"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
  